微博@光年字幕组  官中字幕 • 免费分享 • 请勿商用
Did he try to break it for you?
(楼梯井,地下室入口)
(王-贝克面部表情疼痛评分量表)
你的士兵对你很忠诚
Your soldiers are loyal to you.
I think they're worried we're gonna execute you.
他们似乎在担心我们会处决你
If I was getting executed, Isaac would've come himself.
如果真要处决我,艾萨克会亲自来
There was a shooting near the borderline between us and the Scars.
我们和刀疤帮的边界线附近 发生了一起枪击事件
Treaty might be broken. He's dealing with that now.
可能危及停战协议 他正在处理这件事
如果再次开战 我们会需要所有的士兵
If it's war again, we're gonna need all the soldiers we have.
So he's wondering why you apparently killed some of your own men.
所以他想知道你为什么杀了自己人
Including Leon.
包括里昂
Leon?
里昂
Leon.
Jesus.
天啊
发生了什么事?
What happened?
- My unit is responsible for-- - Securing the hospital.
我的小队负责...
封锁医院,我知道你们的任务 是我下的命令,艾丽丝,怎么回事?
I know your orders. I gave them, Elise. What happened?
We cleared the ground floor up to the sixth.
我们清查了一楼到六楼
有几个分散的感染者 没什么棘手的问题
A few scattered infected here or there. Nothing we couldn't handle.
只剩下地下室了,B1、B2、B3 我们做好了最坏的打算
All that was left was the basement.
B1, B2, B3.
We were expecting the worst, the kind of environment they like.
那是感染者喜欢的环境 而且老一辈的人说
Plus, the old-timers said that down there
2003年第一批虫草菌感染者 就是被带到这里
was where they brought the first Cordyceps patients in '03.
On top of that, we had an access problem.
除此之外 我们还面临着难以进出的问题
These stairwells here, here, and here caved in
这个楼梯井
还有这个和这个都塌陷了
所有电梯厢都卡在了地下井里
and all the elevator cars were stuck in their shafts
just below ground level.
The only way in or out of the basement is here, this stairwell.
进出地下室的唯一通道就是这里 这个楼梯井
所以昨天 我派了一个小队下到B1层
So yesterday, that's where I sent a squad, down to B1.
- 然后呢? - 什么都没发现
- And? - Nothing.
整层楼都是空的,连老鼠都没有
The whole floor was empty, not even rats.
所以今天的目标是B2 我们希望情况和昨天差不多
So today, B2, hoping for more of the same, I sent another squad down
我派了另一队人下去 让里昂负责,因为...
and I put Leon in charge 'cause
他是我最得力的队员
he's my best.
A few minutes in, he radios back.
几分钟后,他呼叫我们说 墙上和地上都有虫草菌
There's Cordyceps on the walls, the floor.
Chances are, they'll find infected next, but that's what they were down there for
接下来,他们很可能会发现感染者
但那正是他们的任务 所以我让他继续前进
so I told him to proceed.
Five minutes later, he radios again.
五分钟后,他又呼叫我们了 但这一次,他...
This time, he...
he was struggling to breathe.
他呼吸困难
He could hardly talk.
几乎说不出话
我以为...
I thought maybe he had been bit.
他可能被咬了
我说“里昂,你被咬了吗?” 而他说...
I said, "Leon, were you bit?" He said...
“就在空气中”
He said, "It's in the air."
He said, "It's in the air.
他说“就在空气中”
“快把我们封在里面”
Seal us in."
我知道通风口里没有病菌 不然我们几周前就被感染了
And I knew it wasn't in the vents
or we would've all been infected weeks ago.
所以我召集了另一支队伍 锁上了通往B2的唯一一扇门
So, I scrambled my other team and we locked the only door to B2
and we locked the only door to B1.
以及通往B1的唯一一扇门
我们照里昂说的做了
And we did what Leon said.
把他们封在里面了
We sealed them in.
Nothing else has gotten out?
没有其他东西跑出来吗?
也没有其他人生病?
No one else has gotten sick?
好
Okay.
The hospital's a resource we can't afford to lose.
那家医院是宝贵的资源 我们不能失去它
我只会告诉那些必须知情的人 不会告诉其他人
I'll inform only the people who absolutely need to know, and no one else.
As far as I'm concerned, Sergeant Park,
朴中士,在我看来
你以果断而英勇的方式解决了危机
you resolved the situation permanently and heroically.
我们欠你一个人情
We owe you a debt.
I'm sorry about your son.
你儿子牺牲了,请节哀
片名:最后生还者
(西雅图)
(第二天)
Patrol 14 heading north to 13th and Bradford.
“14号巡逻队从13街与布拉福街 路口向北行进,已驶出一英里”
One mile out.
One mile out. Copy.
“已驶出一英里,收到”
Mobile three.
(13街与布拉福街路口)
- “三号车” - “三号车”
Mobile three.
“你...”
“蓝队收到”
Possible movement at the convention center.
“会议中心疑似有动静”
“往西北偏北方向...”
- What? - Lights.
- 怎么了? - 有灯了
Oh, good.
很好
They have a big-ass generator down there. Natural gas, baby.
那里有台超大的发电机 天然气的,宝贝
“55,代号4,会议中心...”
- 你弄明白了吗? - 快了
- You figure it out yet? - Gettin' there.
You'll find a safe way to get us to the hospital though, right?
你会找到一条安全路线 带我们去医院的,对吧?
“代号四”
要我帮忙吗?
Can I help?
No.
- 不用 - 为什么?因为我傻吗?
Why, because I'm stupid?
- 我不会用这个词形容你 - 真的吗?那你想用什么词?
That's not the word I would use.
Really? What word then?
Non-school-oriented.
“没上过学”
Fuck you, I went to school. Let me help.
去你的,我上过学,让我帮忙吧
我在做三角定位
I'm triangulating.
- Do you know how that works? - Yes.
- 你会吗? - 会,用三角形定位
With triangles.
It's pretty standard.
其实挺简单的
I get a bearing of their troop movements, and then triangulate back to their bases.
我先确定他们部队的方位
然后三角定位到他们的基地 但我还在估算角度
I'm estimating angles, though.
I mean, if I had a protractor, it would be a lot more accurate.
如果我有量角器,那会更准确
Oh, I actually brought a protractor.
我带了一把量角器
- You did? - No.
- 真的吗? - 假的
我不知道那是什么,而且我讨厌数学
I don't know what that is, and I hated math.
I'm gonna leave you alone now and go and explore
我就不打扰你了,我去探索其他角落
the rest of this place, because you're smart as fuck
反正你聪明绝顶,你会算明白的
and you're figuring it out.
艾莉
- Ellie. - Yes?
怎么了?
If I ever were to lose you
Did you figure it out?
你算明白了吗?
I think so, yeah.
应该是吧
Good.
那就好
We follow a safe path west until this spot.
我们沿着安全路线向西走 直到这个地方
Here, let me show you.
来,我画给你看
They run a line of patrols north and south, like this.
他们的巡逻队是这样南北纵深的
They're pretty evenly spread out, so they're watching that entire area.
分布得很均匀 所以整个区域都在他们的监视中
But there's a gap between here and here.
但这里和这里之间有间隙
Now, on this map, do you see this long-ass building?
回到这张地图上 你看到这栋矩形建筑了吗?
Yeah.
我们穿过这栋楼,然后溜过去
So, we cut through and slip by.
What is that long-ass building?
这栋矩形建筑是什么?
No clue.
不知道
But it's set off from the residential area
但它和住宅区有一定的间隔
so maybe it's a warehouse or something.
可能是仓库之类的
这么大的建筑,他们不可能忽视 为什么没人巡逻?
It's a big fucking something for them just to ignore.
Why aren't they patrolling it?
- 感染者 - 有可能
- Infected. - Probably.
If we make it through, we pop out behind their patrols.
如果我们从楼里穿过去 就会绕到巡逻队的后方
The hospital's maybe a quarter mile from there.
医院离那里大概有四分之一英里
诺拉应该在一楼,北翼的尽头
Nora should be on the first floor, far end of the North Wing.
Wait, how the fuck do you know that?
- 等等,你怎么知道的? - 他们说个不停,我什么都听得见
They never shut up. I hear everything.
Morons. Middle of a fucking war
一群蠢货,战争正打得火热 他们居然暴露自己的位置
and they're just broadcasting their positions.
我一直在想这件事
Yeah, so I've been thinking about that.
You know these people they're fighting, the Scars?
你知道他们的对手刀疤帮吗?
We already know they use bows and arrows, right?
我们已经知道他们使用弓箭了
而且他们像个邪教,或者至少很虔诚
And they seem culty, or at least really religious.
- You ever hear of Amish people? - Amish people? No.
- 你听说过阿米什人吗? - 阿米什人?没有
Well, they were around back in '03, Pennsylvania mostly.
他们在2003年还存在
主要聚集在宾夕法尼亚州 但他们选择过19世纪的生活
But they chose to live like it was the 1800s.
Maybe the Scars are like that? No electricity or technology.
说不定刀疤帮也是那样?
不用电力或科技,因为...
Because these motherfuckers talk on the radio
这些混蛋毫不遮掩地用无线电对话 好像知道没人会听
like they know no one's listening.
对,他们也不在乎少了一个对讲机
Yeah, and they didn't care that a walkie was missing.
It's good. They're overconfident.
这是好事,他们过于自信 就给了我们可乘之机
- It gives us an edge. - It does.
没错
但我们这么做也很鲁莽 算是半斤八两吧
But what we're doing is reckless, so kind of a wash.
如果我们现在出发
If we were to leave now, it'd be dark by the time
等我们到那栋大楼,天就黑了吧?
we got to the big fucking something, right?
Let's go be reckless.
我们去做鲁莽的事吧
你确定这条路安全吗?
Are you sure this way is safe?
You don't trust me?
你信不过我?
- 我信得过你,但我信不过西雅图 - 我也一样
I trust you. I don't trust Seattle.
Me neither, but let's just talk like everything's fine
就假装一切正常吧
because if I get too anxious, I'm gonna barf again.
如果我太焦虑,又会吐的
好,这样吧 你要给孩子取什么名字?
Alright, how 'bout this?
What are you gonna name it?
Oh, if it's a girl, Ellie.
如果是女孩,就叫艾莉 如果是男孩,就叫以利亚
If it's a boy, Elijah.
- Really? - No.
- 真的吗? - 假的
Why? It's a cool name.
为什么?这名字挺酷的
搞什么?
What the fuck?
(感受她的爱)
(感受这个吧,贱人)
We shouldn't be here.
我们不该来这里,一开始就不该来
We shouldn't have come. I shouldn't have dragged you here.
我不该把你拖过来 你要有孩子了,我在干什么?
You're having a fucking baby. What am I doing?
Dina, do you wanna go back?
迪娜?你想回去吗?
I'll take you back. You don't need to do this with me.
我送你回去,你不用陪我的
I'm so fucking stupid.
我真他妈蠢
You know, you never asked me about the first person I killed.
你从没问过我杀的第一个人是谁
Okay. Who?
好吧,是谁?
我小时候住在圣菲北边 一座森林里的小木屋里
When I was little, we lived in a cabin in a forest north of Santa Fe.
周围散布着几家人 但大多数时候只有我们一家子
And there were scattered families around, but mostly it was just us alone.
And I would get so bored cooped up with my mom
和妈妈和妹妹挤在一起 常常让我觉得无聊透顶
and sister, I would just beg them, "Just let me play outside."
我会求她们说“放我出去玩吧”
But my mom was scared
但我妈很害怕,不让我单独出去
and she wouldn't let me go outside alone.
但有一天,我还是出去了
But one day, I just fucking did
我带了一把枪,谁他妈敢惹我?
and I had a gun, so who's gonna fuck with me?
Now, you already know how this story ends
你已经知道最终的结局了
because I don't live in a cabin north of Santa Fe anymore
因为我已经不住圣菲北边的小木屋了
and I don't have a mom or sister anymore.
也没有妈妈和妹妹了
But since everyone's past is fucked
但既然每个人都有凄惨的过去
我们也听过每个人的凄惨故事
and we've all heard everyone's fucked stories,
how do you think this one goes?
你觉得这个故事会怎么发展?
I don't know. Raiders?
我不知道,掠夺者来了?
Just one. And then?
就一个
然后呢?
You got home. They were dead, he was gone.
你回到家,她们死了,他已经跑了?
差不多,但他还在那里
Almost. He was still there.
我听到她们尖叫,就拿着枪跑回去了
I heard them screaming and I ran back with my gun out
but I was too slow because I was fucking eight.
但我跑得太慢了,因为我才八岁
And when he heard me, he turned around, and he looked really startled.
他听到我的声音时 转过身来,一脸的诧异
我朝他开枪时,他就更诧异了
And when I shot him, he looked more startled.
Fuck, I'm so sorry. I didn't know, I thought...
该死,真抱歉,我不知道,我以为...
- How did you get to Jackson? - It doesn't matter.
- 你怎么到杰克逊的? - 那不重要
This is what matters.
重要的是这次行动
不管乔尔给了那些人 什么理由那么对他
Whatever reason Joel gave those people to do what they did,
he didn't deserve that.
他都不该死得那么惨
我常常想...
And I think, what if I hadn't snuck out?
如果我没有偷溜出去呢?
如果我妈妈和妹妹 在我面前被活活打死呢?
What if my mom and sister were beaten to death in front of me?
如果那个混蛋逼我看着他动手呢?
What if that motherfucker made me watch as he did it?
Would it make a difference if my family had hurt his people first?
如果是我的家人先伤害了他的人 我会原谅他吗?
不会
No.
And if I hadn't killed him,
假如我没有杀他...
假如他逃走了...
if he had gotten away,
我保证,我会永远追杀他
I promise you, I would have hunted him down forever.
Forever.
永不放弃
你想回去,我就回去
I'll go back, if you want.
你想继续走,我就继续走
And I'll keep going, if you want.
没有所谓的对错
There's no right answer.
If I die, it's on me.
如果我死了,那只能怪我
不能怪在你头上
It won't be your fault.
So, what do you want to do?
你准备怎么办?
Keep going.
继续走
- Do you see anything? - No. Let's go.
- 你看到什么了吗? - 没有,我们走
Hurry! Down, down, down.
快!趴下
Cover me.
掩护我
At least we're not blocked in.
- 至少我们没有被堵在里面 - 还有两个有利条件
And there are two more positives.
探照灯装得很高,是用来照外面的
The search lights are up high to scan the outside,
which means there'll be no line of sight to the inside.
所以他们看不到里面
Good. What's the other positive?
很好,另一个有利条件是什么?
That door's open, and nothing's come out to kill us, yet.
那扇门是开着的 但没有东西冲出来杀我们
- 暂时没有 - 这太好了
- Great. - Maybe.
也许吧
我去看一眼
- I'm gonna take a peek. - Yeah, you should do that
对,你应该去 毕竟你是那个不会感染的人
because you're the one who can't get infected.
情况如何?
How's it look?
阴森恐怖,但空空如也
Haunted, but empty.
Oh, just like us.
和我们一样
我不是说里面没有感染者
Look, I'm not saying there won't be infected somewhere in there.
老实说,这整栋楼不可能都空着
In fact, there's no fucking way this entire place is empty.
但从逻辑上看 他们不至于成群结队,对吧?
But simple logic, it's not gonna be a horde, right?
这不是地下
We're not underground, and the Wolves
狼帮就在隔壁,有车有灯
are right next door with their vehicles and lights.
成群的感染者不会毫无反应
A horde's not gonna ignore that shit.
可能只有几个离群的 再加几个循声者?
So what, we've got maybe a few strays and a couple clickers?
We can handle that. We've done it like a million times.
那不难搞定,我们干过无数次了
Yeah. We'll be okay.
对,我们不会有事的
But shooting has to be a last resort, okay?
但只有逼不得已才能开枪,知道吗?
Because if the Wolves hear gunfire,
如果狼帮听到枪声 会有一整支军队来追我们
- then we'll have a whole army up our ass. - Fine.
- 好 - 艾莉
- Ellie. - What?
- 干嘛? - 如果情况不妙
If it gets bad, and we have to make a choice
必须在开枪和逃跑之间二选一 我们选逃跑
between shooting or running, we run.
Last resort, I got it.
逼不得已才开枪,我知道了
你以为不管怎么样 我都会无脑开枪?
Oh, you think that no matter what happens, I'm just gonna start firing?
Literally every single time. Yes.
每一次都是这样
别生气,你这人有点疯 跟你在一起很刺激
Don't get angry. You're a little crazy.
And that's exciting. It's one of the reasons I love you.
这也是我爱你的原因之一 但我真的想活着离开这里
But I do wanna make it out of here.
You love me?
你爱我?
- I re-- - Oh, I know.
- 我真的... - 我知道
再跟我说一遍,计划是什么?
So, tell me again, what's the plan?
Knives or run.
用刀或逃跑
好的,疯子
Okay, Crazy.
走吧
Here we go.
目前为止,情况还不错
So far, so good.
Wait.
等等
Do you hear something?
你听见什么了吗?
没有
No.
So, this way then?
那走这边?
Yeah.
好
这里有很多窗户,小心点
Lots of windows in here. Let's be careful.
Okay.
好
Dina.
迪娜
What the fuck is that? And why is it hiding?
那是什么鬼东西?怎么还躲起来了?
I think it's a smart one,
应该是聪明的那种 就像上次在超市跟踪我的那个
like the one that stalked me at the supermarket.
Okay, but you killed that one, so we can kill this one too, right?
好吧,上次那个死在了你手里 这次也没问题,对吧?
确实死在了我手里,但我先被咬了
Yes, I killed it. Not before it got me.
- It fucking bit you? - What was I supposed to do, tell you?
你被咬了?
不然我能怎么办?告诉你吗?你会...
You would've--
Listen, if it's like the other one,
听着,如果这个和上次的一样
it's gonna be fast and it's gonna be sneaky.
就一定会行动迅速、悄无声息
But this time, it's two on one.
但这次是二打一
Now, that fucker's gonna try to flank us, so I say we flank it first.
那混蛋想从侧面攻击我们 不如我们先下手,分头从两侧攻上去
We split up. Whichever one it follows,
不管他追击谁 另一个人都可以从后面干掉他
the other one comes up and takes it out from behind.
Plan?
怎么样?
Plan.
就这么办
- What do we do? - I don't know.
- 现在怎么办? - 我不知道
Let's go back the way we came.
- 原路返回吧 - 好
If we run, they're gonna chase so we have to go slow.
我们一跑,他们就会追上来 所以我们得慢一点
You see that fencing over there? I'm gonna lure as many as I can.
看到那边的围栏了吗? 我尽量引开他们
You're gonna run in there, secure the gate,
你跑进去 想办法关上门,千万别出来
secure it however you can, and stay in there.
迪娜,我可以随便咬 但你不行,照我说的做
Dina. I can get bit a lot. You can't. Do as I say.
Go!
快去!
- 你被咬了吗? - 什么?没有
- Did you get bit? - What? No.
She's okay.
她没事!我一直看着呢,他们没咬她
I was watching. They didn't bite her.
Jesse, I swear.
杰西,我发誓!
We gotta go.
我们得走了
他们在那里!
Move! Move! Move!
快追!
Don't stop! Keep going!
别停!继续跑!
I'll shoot 'em! Go!
快跑!快!
Heading west!
往西跑!
Over there! Over there!
在那里!
去公园! 我们可以在那里甩掉他们!快!
The park! We can lose 'em in there. Come on!
停,我们不能进去
Stop. Stop. We don't go in there.
Looks like five, three unknowns, chased into the park. Heavily armed.
西湖五号 有三个身份不明者被追进了公园
- 全副武装,不是刀疤帮 - 他们在干什么?
- Not Scars. - What are they doing?
- 停下了 - 如果他们想出来,射杀他们
If they try and come out, shoot 'em.
Not coming in the park.
- 他们不打算进公园 - 你在开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
Great. More infected.
这下好了,又有感染者
Maybe, but we can't go back that way.
也许吧,但我们不能往回走
Come on.
走吧
Jesse.
杰西
- 杰西 - 干嘛?
- What? - How did you find us?
- 你怎么找到我们的? - 你们在剧院留了地图
The map you left in the theater.
- 对了,三角定位技术不错 - 谢谢,那是迪娜的功劳
Impressive triangulation, by the way.
Thanks, that was all Dina.
Trust me, I didn't think it was you.
- 我没想过是你 - 你怎么找到剧院的?
How did you find the theater?
你觉得我现在想跟你说话吗?
Do I look like I wanna fucking talk to you right now?
你一个人来的?
You came alone?
No. Me and Tommy.
不,还有汤米 我们进城后分开了,搜索范围更广
We split up when we got to the city.
- Cover more ground. - I can't believe they sent you after us.
- 他们竟然派你们来找我们 - 他们没有
They didn't, but you two were gonna die out here
但你们两个肯定会死在这里
so we snuck out the next night. And it's a good thing we did.
所以我们第二天晚上就溜出来了 幸好我们来了
You know what, we were doing pretty fucking good
- 我们本来挺好的,直到... - 直到什么?
- up until-- - Up until what?
Until we weren't.
直到我们出了事
Is Tommy okay?
汤米没事吧?
Hopefully.
希望没事,我们说好明早碰头的
We're supposed to rendezvous in the morning.
- So, what now? - Find a way out,
现在怎么办?
想办法出去,返回剧院 暂时度过今晚
get back to the theater, shelter for the night.
然后跟汤米碰头,一起回家
Meet up with Tommy, and then we all go home.
- No. - Ellie.
- 不 - 艾莉
那是什么声音?
What the fuck is that?
走
Hey. Go.
不,等等,求你了,等等! 我跟其他人不一样
No, wait, please. Please, please, please!
I'm not like the others. Please.
拜托,等等,我加入!我加入你们
No, no, no, wait. Wait, wait, I'll join!
- I'll join you. I'll join. - Too late, Wolf.
太迟了,狼崽子
No, no. No, no, no, wait! I know things.
不,等等,我知道一些事 我知道艾萨克的计划
I know what Isaac is planning. I can help you. I can--
我可以帮你们,我可以...
We have no interest in your words.
我们对你说的话没兴趣 因为腐败的灵魂只会撒谎
"For the corrupted soul knows only lies."
这是先知的教导
So taught the Prophet.
May She guide us.
- 愿她指引我们 - 愿她指引我们
No. No. No. No. No.
不
不,求你们,拜托,不要啊
No. No, no, no. Please, please, please. No.
No. No.
不
No! No! No!
No.
不...
- 求你们 - 他在罪恶中筑巢
Oh, please, please, no.
He is nested in sin.
- No, no. - Free him,
- 给他自由,使他得见她的爱 - 给他自由,使他得见她的爱
that he may know Her love.
No, no. No, no, no, no.
不!求你们,不要啊
Please, please, please, no.
天啊,不要啊
Now, he is free.
他自由了
Oh, fuck!
该死!
我把他们引开,带她出去,快! 我们剧院见!快跑!
I'll lead them away. Get her out. Go!
I'll meet you back at the theater. Fucking go!
你逃不掉的,狼崽子! 她看到你了,她看顾着我们所有人!
You won't get away, Wolf. She sees you.
She watches over us all.
He's not here.
她不在这里
愿她指引我们
- May She guide us. - May She guide us.
Alright, spread out. Keep moving.
好了,分头搜
What do we got?
- “什么情况?” - 不确定,我去看看
Not sure. Checking it out.
Come on, Bonnie.
走吧,邦妮
It was a critter or something.
是只小动物什么的,安全
All clear.
You're all set.
好了
把那东西放下
Put that shit down.
举起双手,转过身来
Hands up. Turn around.
你记得我吗?
You remember me?
Yeah, you remember me.
对,你记得我
你想干什么?
- What do you want? - Where's Abby?
艾比在哪里?
- I don't know. - Yes, you do.
- 我不知道 - 你知道
You shoot me, the sound will have every soldier come running.
只要你开枪 所有士兵都会被枪声吸引过来
You'll still be dead.
但你还是会死的
告诉我她在哪里,也许我会放你走
Tell me where she is and maybe I let you go.
- 我们饶了你一命 - 你们就不该犹豫
- We could've killed you. - Maybe you should have.
Or maybe you should've stayed the fuck out of Jackson, Nora.
你们当初就不该去杰克逊,诺拉
Where's Abby?
艾比在哪里?
I'm sorry you saw it happen.
很抱歉让你目睹了那一切
没人应该目睹那种惨剧
No one should ever have to see something like that.
- 闭嘴 - 有时候
- Stop it. - Sometimes at night,
我还会在夜里听到他的叫喊声
I still hear his screams.
他死得太惨了
It was a terrible thing, the way he died.
Yeah.
是啊
Yeah, the little bitch got what he deserved.
那个贱人罪有应得
王八蛋!
Motherfucker!
入侵者!
Intruder!
来人啊,射死她!
Hey! Shoot her!
妈的!
不...
Oh, no, no, no, no.
诺拉,你死定了!
Nora, you're gonna fucking die!
Nora!
诺拉!
(B2)
Fuck, it's open.
该死,门开了
The fucking shaft is open!
那个竖井打开了!
- Seal off the hallway! - Back, back, back!
封锁走廊!快!
室内一号,那个竖井打开了
The shaft is open.
(电气室)
You stupid bitch.
你这个愚蠢的贱人
孢子
Spores.
We're breathing spores.
我们正在吸入孢子
我们被感染了
We're infected.
You killed us both.
你把我们俩都害死了
是吗?
Did I?
You're...
你...你是她
You're her.
The immune girl, you're...
那个免疫的女孩,你真的存在
You're real.
对
Yeah.
Where's Abby?
艾比在哪里?
你不知道他做了什么吗?
Don't you know what he did?
- I don't care. - You don't care?
我不在乎
你不在乎?
他杀了...
He killed everyone in that hospital.
那个医院里的所有人
包括唯一一个 能从你身上找到解药的人
Including the only fucking person alive that could make a cure from you.
那是艾比的父亲
That was Abby's father.
而乔尔...
And Joel...
乔尔朝他的头开了一枪
Joel shot him in the head.
这就是他干的好事
That's what he did.
I know.
我知道
Where's Abby?
艾比在哪里?
不
No.
她在哪里?
Where is she?
不
No.
Where is she?
- 她在哪里? - 不
No.
Where is she?!
她在哪里?
Hey, kiddo.
嘿,小家伙
微博@光年字幕组  官中字幕 • 免费分享 • 请勿商用
Hi.
嗨
待续
谢谢观赏
译者: 邹琳